# Sri Harsha Kantipudi Hamburg, Germany

Email: kvsharsha9010@qmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/harshakantipudi

Phone: +91 9010427829 Git-hub: <a href="https://github.com/harshakantipudi">https://github.com/harshakantipudi</a>

# **Profile Summary**

Skilled Data enthusiast, motivated & energetic and Around 5 years of Professional IT Experience working on **FMCG-Business-Intelligence**, Python, **ERP, AWS, Marketing** Operations. I believe in making life fun and exciting with code and visualization. I love contributing to the Open-Source Domain, digging deeper in the field of **Data Intelligence (MLOps)** 

# Work Experience

09.2020- Till date

## Vivere GmbH, Hamburg, Germany Data scientist Responsibilities:

- Implemented **Odoo ERP** system for the inhouse backend support by using RESTful API (**Python**)
- Designed & Implemented BI-Layer on the top of ODOO ERP & Leading
  Business intelligence architecture of organization.
- Responsible for Data collection, Quality monitoring by MLOps operations
- Working with multiple data sources (DWH, PostgreSQL) to create reports in Tableau, Looker.
- Created automated report generation script using Python-Google sheets for marketing, Procurement, Inventory.
- Developed a Machine learning model for **Demand forecasting**.
- Created Open order reports for advance reporting and Data analysis for various business units and prototype building in SQL and Python.
- Researched and Identified Keyword market (Google Trends &
  Amazon Market place) for new product development in FMCG.
- Scraping the Instagram and to analyze influencers performance.
- Implemented a Regression model to manage stock levels.

08.2016 - 10.2019

HCL Technologies, Chennai, India Software Engineer, 06.2016 - 10.2019 Client: Teradyne (USA)

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Performed requirement analysis designing, maintaining the
  Datawarehouse, dbt based on the Software Architecture.
- Creating ETL pipelines in terms of getting the data, building the pipelines
  & scheduling the scripts using Airflow
- Responsible in providing high-quality data on time to stakeholders.

- Identifying **KPI's** and **metrics** for procurement, Sales, Marketing
- Worked with **AWS IAM** service creating new users & roles and policies
- Implemented **DevOps** Continuous Integration (**CI/CD**) using **Jenkins**
- Created **Python** Scripts to Automate **AWS** services, database security groups, S3 and application configuration
- Gained experience in several diverse branches, such as FMCG, Marketing and supply chain.
- Maintaining crucial relationships with the company's investors by preparing monthly KPI reporting

#### Education

10.2019 – 12.2020 University of Bologna (Unibo), Bologna, Italy

**Course of study: Master's degree in Data Science**, Grade – 2.8 **Focus**- fields: Machine learning, Data Mining, Business Intelligence and Data warehousing, Bigdata, Python, Digital analytics, Marketing analytics

06.2012 – 06.2016 KL University, Vijayawada, India

Course of study: B.Tech. Electronics Engineering, 7.4 GPA

#### IT Skills

Project Management: Agile, Scrum, Crisp-Dm

**Programming**: C++, Python, R, YAML (Beginner)

**Databases**: PostgreSQL, ODOO ERP

**Data science**: Regression, Decision Tree, Clustering Time series analysis

**Visualization Tools :** Tableau, Power-BI, Looker (Beginner)

Cloud Technologies: AWS (EC2, S3, IAM, Lambda, VPC, Route53), Sage Maker, Terraform

Other Tools : Data Grip, Visual studio, Jenkins, Docker, Git, Airflow

### Achievements and Certifications

 AWS Certified solution Architect Associate – Validity till March 2023 (Verify: https://www.credly.com/earner/earned/badge/)

Awarded 6000-euro merit scholarship at university of Bologna in the year 2019-20

#### **Projects**

**Business Intelligence Layer on the top of ERP systems:** Objective behind this project is to implement a BI-Layer for ERP systems. Collected a data from FMCG companies and processed using a ETL pipeline to PostgreSQL database. Finally, on the top of this created a data modelling and reporting layer using Power BI and Data studio

**Inventory and Metrics Monitoring Application:** Identified business requirements and metrics for inventory and created a web application dashboard which is used for monitoring. Created Flask framework (API) and deployed container on Docker.